Guide to the Ford Madox Ford collection, [ca. 1850]-1973
Ford, Ford Madox collection,
- Series III. Incoming correspondence and manuscripts by others
  - E-F
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, Mar.27, 1907; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 87)
      Durham; Dear Violet, R says you may be going to W.G's for Easter, if so I conclude you will come here [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy,fragment] to Violet Hunt, [Apr., 1907]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 88)
      Durham; ... you yesterday. I was so busy, and had to take R. to dentist and to get clothes. [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [May, 1907]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 89)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Have it your own way. I want Mamma & I do not want a disagreeable correspondence [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, May 11, 1907; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 90)
      Durham; Dear Violet, You must have got my letter by now, though to make sure I will send a wire. [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, [Jul.26, 1907]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 91)
      Durham; Dear Violet, All right - I will meet train Wednesday, 24. It must be a squeeze - [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, [Aug., 1907?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 92)
      Durham; Dear Violet, It will be nice if you will come in September, bringing Miss D. and Miss H. [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, Nov.14, [1907?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 93)
      Durham; Dear Violet/ When I see you in the winter I will tell you R's delinquencies. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Apr., 1908?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 94)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Please excuse blots, I am being economical. The sun hats are for the children [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [May, 1908]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 95)
      Durham; Dear Violet- I cannot arrange exactly about R yet. Of course she will be passing through London [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun./Jul., 1908?]; 2 leaves + 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 96)
      Durham; Dear Violet, I cannot write with any degree of cheerfulness. Life does inflict such terrible wounds. [Second copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun., 1908?]; 2 leaves + 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 97)
      Durham; Dear Violet. I was waiting to send these few things until the laundry came, [Second copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun., 1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 98)
      Durham; Dear Violet/ Thanks for your nice letter. I only got it last night. I was away for a night. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun., 1908?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 99)
      Durham; Dear Violet. I have considered the matter well, & we thrashed it out well together. [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun., 1908?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 100)
      Durham; Dear Violet. Don't let R. go anywhere alone with Martin Muir, or any man, [Second copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jun.20, 1908?]; 1 leaf + 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 101)
      Durham; Dear Violet. I think I should come on the 29th, & should prefer to go on straight. [Second copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jul./Aug., 1908?]; 1 leaf + 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 102)
      Durham; Dear Violet. I am a great deal better, so don't fuss about me. [Second copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, [Jul., 1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 103)
      Durham; Dear Violet, I cannot arrange about R yet. Of course she will be passing through London [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy, fragment] to Violet Hunt, [Jul., 1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 104)
      Durham; Dear V, I daresay it is all right, and I am sure you are as economical as possible [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy, fragment] to Violet Hunt, [Jul., 1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 105)
      Durham; I realized last summer a little what a pretty grown up girl meant. [Copy typed by Hunt.] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, [Jul. 18, 1908?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 106)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Why say such very nasty things. Had Mamma over appealed to me to come here, [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jul.27, 1908]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 107)
      Durham; Dear Violet, We have another small dance, ahouse-party dance, [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, [Jul./Aug., 1908?]; 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 108)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Thanks for your nice letter. I only got it last night. [Copy typed by Hunt.] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Aug. 1908/09?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 109)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Neither Walton nor I want R. to go away again. [Second copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [1909/1910?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 110)
      Durham; Dear Violet/ Please don't worry me. I have done this entirely for R's good- [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt TL[copy,fragment] to Violet Hunt, [1909]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 111)
      Durham; ... but I am not, and have not had a chance to be. [Copy and carbon typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jan./Feb.,1909?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 112)
      Durham; Dear Violet, If there's the slightest suspicion of R having such a serious thing as Glaucoma, [Typed copy by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jul.,1909]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 112)
      Durham; Dear Violet, I enclose your letter. You will see you speak of "a few days", [Typed copy by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Jul.,1909?]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 114)
      Durham; Dear Violet, My better-ness is only to the extent of being raised up in bed, [Typed copy by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, Jul.26, [1909]; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 115)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Please explain what the item, hat .1.13 [pounds] is for. [Typed copy by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Aug.5, 1909?]; 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 116)
      Durham; Dear Violet, Thanks for the paper & magazine, I can read more now. [Typed copy by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, [Aug.6, 1908?]; 2 leaves + 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 117)
      Durham; Dear Violet, You ask me about M. Well, she is not fit to be without a regular medical attendant, [Typed copy by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fogg Elliot, Silvia Hunt ALS to Violet Hunt, Nov.3, [1909?]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 118)
      Durham; Dear Violet. Nothing you say will make me change my mind. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Aug.16, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 119)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: Under separate cover we are sending you with our compliments [Signed Edward F. Healey]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Mar.30, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 120)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford, Of course I like the idea of having you back in the Forum [Signed Henry Goddard Leach]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Jun.23, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 121)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford: I am proud to accept "The Fate of the semi-Classic" for early publication [Signed Henry Goddard Leach]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Sept.20, 1937; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 122)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford, I am enclosing advance proof of an amusing essay [Signed Henry Goddard Leach]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Jan.31, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 123)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford, To me you are always a miracle. [Signed Henry Goddard Leach]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, Feb.10, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 124)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford, Here is a corrected and very slightly cut edition of your article. [Signed P. Moir]
    - The Forum TLS to Ford, May 17, 1938; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 125)
      New York; Dear Mr. Ford, Your article on the French has us all on the fence. [Signed Henry Goddard Leach]
    - Foster, Jeanne Roberts TL[copy] to William A. Bradley, Nov.29, 1926; 2 leaves (Box 55, Folder 125.5)
      Boston; Dear Mr. Bradley: Mr. Ferris Greenslet is very enthusiastic about Mr. Ford. [Julian Loewe papers]
    - Foster, Jeanne Roberts ALS to Ford, Oct.27, 1930; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 126)
      Boston; My dear F.M.F. Hearing from you via Longmans Green and Co.'s tea was thrilling
    - Foster, Jeanne Roberts TLS to Arthur Mizener, May 27, 1968; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 55, Folder 126.5)
      Schenectady; Dear Mr. Mizener, Your letter of May 23d, 1968 received.
    - France. Ministere de l'instruction publique. Bibliotheque et Musee de la guerre TLS to Ford, May 31, 1919; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 127)
      Paris; Dear Sir, I have the honour to call you attention to the enclosed summary on the BIBLIOTHEQUE ET MUSEE DE LA GUERRE. [Signed Pierre Rany]
    - Franks, Sir Augustus Wollaston ALS to Margaret Raine (Mrs. Alfred) Hunt, Jan.6, 1880; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 55, Folder 128)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hunt, The fates are after all unpropitious. I have just learnt that one of my colleagues [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Franks, Sir Augustus Wollaston ALS to Margaret Raine (Mrs. Alfred) Hunt, Mar.8, 1881; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 55, Folder 129)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hunt, I should be very glad to be useful to you in the matter of the glass wares; [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fraser, Grace Lovat ALS to Arthur Mizener, Oct.11, 1967; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 55, Folder 129.5)
      [London] Dear Professor Mizener, You must have thought me very discourteous not to have answered your letter of Aug 16th. [Gift of Arthur and Rosemary Mizener]
    - Freeling, Sir Francis Envelope to Rev. James Raine, May 9, 1834; 1 envelope (Box 55, Folder 130)
      Envelope addressed to Raine from Freeling [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Freemantle, W. T. TL[copy] to Elizabeth Eleanor Higgins, May 9, 1923; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 131)
      Sheffield; Dear Madam,In reply to your letter of 1st instant, I am sorry I cannot give the information [Copy typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Freemantle, W. T. TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, May 9, 1923; 6 leaves + 6 leaves (Box 55, Folder 132)
      Rotherham; Dear Madam, I was glad to receive yours of the 7th inst:- I tried my utmost to sweep away the rubbish [Two copies typed by Hunt][Violet Hunt papers]
    - Freemantle, W. T. TL[copy,fragment] to Violet Hunt, May 22, 1923; 3 leaves (Box 55, Folder 133)
      Rotherham; Dear Madam, I am very sorry I have not acknowledged the Book you so kindly sent [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Freemantle, W. T. TL[copy,fragment] to Violet Hunt, Jun.22, 1923; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 134)
      [Rotherham]; You will have no difficulty in finding the Chapel (now Picture Hall) [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frewer, J.E. & Co.AD to Margaret Rain (Mrs. Alfred) Hunt, Feb.16, 1899; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 135)
      [London] Bill and receipt for scotch for M. Hunt, Esq. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frey, Sheila ALS to Violet Hunt, Apr.8, [n.y.]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 136)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer, We should be so pleased if you could come to dinner on Friday, [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frey, Sheila ALS to Violet Hunt, Nov.10 [n.y.]; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 137)
      London; Dear Mrs. Hueffer, Thank you so much for asking us to dinner on Saturday. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Fripp, Alfred D. ALS to Alfred William Hunt, Jan.28, 1878; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 138)
      London; My dear Hunt, I shall be happy to form your table at the A.G. B. Dinner and help to swell your number [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frith, Miss & M.F. Frith AD to anonymous, Mar.31, 1899; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 139)
      London; [Bill and receipt for flowerpot] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frost, Edwin Hunt [Printed clipping] An Interesting letter from Spain, Feb.6, 1929; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 140)
      Ohio; [One page article from The Republic Reporter of Republic, Ohio for Sept.12, 1929.]
    - Frost, Edwin Hunt TLS to Violet Hunt, Aug.5, 1929; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 141)
      Yonkers, NY; My dear Violet: Here we are home again [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frost, Edwin Hunt TLS to Violet Hunt, Sept.30, 1929; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 142)
      Yonkers, NY; Dear Violet: How are you, for we have not heard a word from you [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Frost, Edwin Hunt TLS to Violet Hunt, Aug.10, 1929; 1 leaf (Box 55, Folder 143)
      Yonkers, NY; My dear Violet: Ever since our arrival at home, just two weeks from today [Violet Hunt papers]
  - G
    - G., B. B. AL[postcard]S to Margaret Raine (Mrs. Alfred) Huntt, Sept.13, 1907; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 1)
      Westmorland; My dear Mrs. Hunt - I hope you are having a nice change. I am enjoying a lovely trip [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Gaie, Crosby TLS to Ford, Mar.3, 1928; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 2)
      New York; My dear Ford, Your letter of February 2oth, together with the corrected "O Hymen" essay
    - Galsworthy, John ALS to Ford, Oct.19, 1906; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 3)
      London; My dear Hueffer, You've mistaken my meaning. I never supposed for a minute
    - Galsworthy, John TL[copy] to Ford, Oct.4, 1908; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 4)
      London; My dear Heuffer. If you really want to print a selection of my verse, [Two copies typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Galsworthy, John TLS to Ford, Nov.14, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 5)
      London; My dear Hueffer, Well, well! I'm loth to think it's the last of our walks and talks, [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Galsworthy, John TL[copy] to Violet Hunt, Mar.12, 1908; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 6)
      London; My dear Miss Hunt/ Yesterday was the first day I could get to really read your book, [Copy typed by Hunt] [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Galton, Francis AL[postcard]S to Mrs. Robb, Jul.27, 1898; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 7)
      London; Cambo is the charming place - like apiece of the lower parts of the Highlands [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Garbutt, R.H.O. ALS to Violet Hunt, May 1, 1909; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 8)
      Durham; Dear Miss Hunt, I must first thank you very much for kindly sending me Tona-Bungay. [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Garland, A.J. AL[postcard]S to Violet Hunt, Mar.15, 1923; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 9)
      Cannes, France; I am sorry that I cannot give you any information respecting Mr. & Mrs. Howell [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Garnett, David ALS to Ford, [1892]; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 10)
      [London] My dear Hueffer, I send you at last a copy of The Brown Owl
    - Garnett, David AL[postcard]S to Arthur Mizener, [Dec., n.y.]; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 11)
      [London?] Best wishes for a Merry Christmas & a Happy New York
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.12, 1965; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 12)
      Huntingdon; Dear Dr. Mizener, I had heard about your expedition to the [Cearne?] I haven't been for a long time
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.26, 1965; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 13)
      Huntingdon; Dear Dr. Mizener, Thank you for your letter & offer of hospitality
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, Mar.2, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 14)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Mizener, I assume your are now back in the United States and so I am sending this to Cornell.
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, Mar.21, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 15)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Mizener, Thank you so much for your letter and what you have arranged
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, Apr.18, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 16)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Mizener, I got your letter this morning and hasten to reply
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Jul.27, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 17)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Mizener, I am sorry to have to trouble you about my visa. I have the ordinary tourist visa
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Oct.31, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 18)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Mizener, Very many thanks for your letter about the visas. Stanford, Cal. has now produced a permit
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.2, 1966; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 19)
      Huntingdon; Dear Dr. Mizener, I am so sorry I wrote a rather petulant letter. I shall be delighted to give a lecture
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Nov.28, 1966; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 20)
      Stanford; Dear Mizener -- or may I say dear Arthur? I want to thank you again for all the time you lavished on me
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Dec.7, 1966; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 21)
      Davis,CA; Dear Arthur, Thank you so much for your letter which has just come on here.
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, May 6, 1967; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 22)
      Huntingdon; Dear Professor Meizener, [sic] I have been meaning to write to you for a long time
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, May 21, 1967; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 23)
      Huntingdon; Dear Arthur, I was so glad to get your letter and that you think I have not been remiss
    - Garnett, David TLS to Arthur Mizener, Oct.2, 1967; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 24)
      St. Martin-de-Vers; Dear Arthur, Your letter has been forwarded to me here and I want to thank you for it.
    - Garnett, David ALS to Arthur Mizener, Jan.6, 1969; 1 leaf + envelope (Box 56, Folder 25)
      Huntingdon; Dear Arthur, Thank you for your delightful and so flattering letter. I am so pleased that you liked Quentin
    - Garnett, Martha ALS to Ford, Aug.13, 1905; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 26)
      [London] Dear Ford/ As Elsie is not at home, I address myself to you and the absorbing dometic topic of cooks.
    - Garanett, Martha ALS to Olive Garnett, Jul.6, 1939; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 27)
      Bridport; Dear Olive, Here is the Sunday Tumes" article -- fortunately not destroyed, as I feared it might be.
    - Garnett, Olivia R. AL[fragment]S to [Elsie Martindale Hueffer?], [1930's?]; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 28)
      [n.p.] ... How does yr. wireless go? My 14 yr. old one pegged out at Xmas
    - Garnett, Olivia R. ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Jun.28, 1939; 2 leaves (Box 56, Folder 29)
      [n.p.] My dear Elsie, I had not heard. I opened Lucy's letter with the news first, & then yours,
    - Garnett, Olivia R. ALS to Katharine Hueffer Lamb, Feb.25, 1945; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 30)
      Berkshire; Dear Katharine, Instinct, reason & my condition forbid my helping you in a painful & difficult position
    - Garnett, Olivia R. ALS to Katharine Hueffer Lamb, Feb.25, 1949; 2 leaves + envelope (Box 56, Folder 31)
      Berkshire; My dear Babs, Our letters crossed, now I write again to thank you for yr. second
    - Garnett, Richard S. ALS to Ford, Dec.12, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 32)
      Hampstead; My dear Ford, I have been very long in thanking you and Mr. Conrad
    - Garnett, Richard S. TLS to Katharine Hueffer Lamb, Apr.23, 1945; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 33)
      London; Dear Mrs. Lamb, I was so glad to hear from you again
    - Garnett, Richard S. TD List of Sale Prices, Nov.21-23, 1928; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 34)
      [n.p.] [One page list of sale prices]
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Unknown, [n.d.]; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 35)
      [n.p.] Miss [S?] has sent a cheque today. [Verso contains AD Vita of Alfred William Hunt from the Encyclopedia Britannica.]
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Joseph Conrad, Jul.11, 1901; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 36)
      [n.p.] My dear Conrad, Ford Hueffer writes to me to-day about an advance which he contemplates making you
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton AL[copy]S to Joseph Conrad, Jul.13, 1901; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 37)
      London; My dear Conrad, I thank you for your letter of yesterday. Like you, I am going to write quite frankly.
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Ford, Jul.16, 1901; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 38)
      London; Dear Ford, Conrad: I received your letter this morning instructing me to let Conrad have 60 pounds
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Ford, [1909]; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 39)
      London; Dear Ford, To decline to see M would be a very great mistake for you [Violet Hunt papers]
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, [n.d.]; 2 leaves (Box 56, Folder 40)
      Aldington; Dear Elsie, A gentleman, who said that he had already, tho' some time since, corresponded with you
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, [n.d.]; 2 leaves (Box 56, Folder 41)
      London; Dear Elsie, A line to acknowledge your letter received here last night
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, [Dec.1,]1902; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 42)
      London; Dear Elsie, Wilson has now sent me the accounts. I will go carefully through and then send them back to you
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Dec.22, 1902; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 43)
      London; Dear Elsie, Your Father's Estate/ Enclosed I send Capital Account/ Income Account/ Trading Account
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Jan.21, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 44)
      London; Dear Elsie, Your Father's Estate/ For your convenience, I have had my Queries and Wilsons Replies
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Jan.24, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 45)
      London; re: Mrs. Martindale/ Dear Elsie, In reply to yours - I think your Mother will have to be told
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.4, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 46)
      London; Wm. Martindale deed: Dear Elsie, I have your letter and [?] this evening. I should think you might reply to your Mother
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Feb.19, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 47)
      London; re Martindale: Dear Elsie, In reply to your letter - I think it is quite time I wrote to Wilson again.
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Mar.11, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 48)
      London; re Wm. Martindale: Dear Elsie, In reply to your letter, I last heard from Wilson on Feb.24th
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Mar.20, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 49)
      London; Mrs. Martindale: Private; Dear Elsie, Yours just received. You had better cash the cheque
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Mar.27, 1903; 1 leaf + 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 50)
      London; Dear Elsie, re Wm. Martindale: Your brother wants a receipt for that 20 pounds. [Enclosed is AL[copy]S of Robert Garnett to Wilson & Sons, 27 March 1903.]
    - Garnett, Robert Singleton ALS to Elsie Martindale Hueffer, Apr.14, 1903; 1 leaf (Box 56, Folder 51)
      London; Dear Elsie, I called at Messrs. Wilson & Sons office this afternoon